[{"answer": "Never.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 17, "question": "Will you ever get over this?", "qSentId": 16}, {"answer": "It was a great evening.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 32, "question": "Rob, what was it like?", "qSentId": 31}, {"answer": "Well, I think there was -- there has been a lot of enthusiasm for President Obama before his position on marriage equality.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 45, "question": "Did the stand he took over gay marriage, do you think, get him right back into the Hollywood firmament in one big hit?", "qSentId": 44}, {"answer": "Well, I mean, I would say that it's -- if the other side decides that they're not going to spend any money on the campaign, then I would say that he probably shouldn't go look for places to raise money.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 57, "question": "What do you say to that?", "qSentId": 56}, {"answer": "I think he's done remarkably well.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 66, "question": "If you're -- if you're putting an overview on his performance so far, how do you think he's done?", "qSentId": 65}, {"answer": "Well, I don't know what his thoughts about that are, but I knew -- I don't know that if he ever decides to run for elected office, he'd be terrific.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 82, "question": "What do you think?", "qSentId": 81}, {"answer": "You know, I think it's best to leave these decisions up to the individual mom.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 120, "question": "I mean, a 3-year-old boy suckling on his mother's breast, it's ridiculous, isn't it?", "qSentId": 119}, {"answer": "Well, the U.N. Foundation came together with Every Child by Two to start raising awareness and funds for vaccination campaigns in developing countries -- which I do think is, you know, one of the great medical interventions of our time.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 135, "question": "Why are you so fixated on people getting vaccinations for their kids?", "qSentId": 134}, {"answer": "You know, if you look at the data and the science behind these studies, it seems fairly clear that vaccines are very safe.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 144, "question": "I mean, do you feel these are dangerous statements by celebrities when they say that kind of thing?", "qSentId": 143}, {"answer": "I think probably in most things, yes.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 159, "question": "Are you on the same political side as Mr. Clooney?", "qSentId": 158}, {"answer": "You betcha.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 165, "question": "Yes, will you be voting for Mr. Obama come November?", "qSentId": 164}, {"answer": "Well, on Mother's Day, I will be with my mother and my mother- in-law.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 168, "question": "Finally, Amanda, how are you spending Mother's Day?", "qSentId": 167}, {"answer": "I do.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 216, "question": "You -- do you like doing the interviews?", "qSentId": 215}, {"answer": "Yes, sir.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 236, "question": "You've got a 3-year-old boy, right?", "qSentId": 235}, {"answer": "My first reaction was that -- that must be like a European cover version of \"TIME.\"", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 241, "question": "What was your honest gut reaction?", "qSentId": 240}, {"answer": "I don't think that's actually how she breastfeeds him at three, but --", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 247, "question": "(INAUDIBLE)?", "qSentId": 246}, {"answer": "Not deeply, because she's so attractive.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 251, "question": "Don't you just feel deeply uncomfortable looking at that picture?", "qSentId": 250}, {"answer": "-- you don't get in the business of telling moms what to do, number one.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 266, "question": "Doesn't he go to school?", "qSentId": 265}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 288, "question": "There has to be limits, doesn't there?", "qSentId": 287}, {"answer": "Us.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 293, "question": "Who draws it?", "qSentId": 292}, {"answer": "No, I don't think so.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 299, "question": "-- at cover of \"TIME\" how to -- how to look after her kids?", "qSentId": 298}, {"answer": "Yes, very pleased.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 320, "question": "Were you pleased?", "qSentId": 319}, {"answer": "I think you -- I think if you -- if you feel this way on the issue for same-sex marriage, you have to applaud the president for his -- for his bravery in coming out with his personal opinion, right, and stay there.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 329, "question": "-- that this is going to force the pace or could it actually create more resistance in a certain sense?", "qSentId": 328}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 334, "question": "You study theology?", "qSentId": 333}, {"answer": "I considered it.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 338, "question": "How close were you?", "qSentId": 337}, {"answer": "-- but the words Carson Daly and celibacy aren't --", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 355, "question": "Yes?", "qSentId": 354}, {"answer": "ALY: No, I -- listen, I worked hard and, you know, I dropped out of college and I ended up, you know, broke and living in six cities in California and working in music.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 368, "question": "A reasonably naughty boy?", "qSentId": 367}, {"answer": "I want to say thank you to everybody that voted for me.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 394, "question": "What's going on in your mind?", "qSentId": 393}, {"answer": "Very, very attached.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 407, "question": "How attached do you get to creating a bona fide star?", "qSentId": 406}, {"answer": "It is.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 461, "question": "Life is good for you at the moment, isn't it?", "qSentId": 460}, {"answer": "I've never been happier ever.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 466, "question": "I mean, personally, you've probably, I would imagine, never been happier, right?", "qSentId": 465}, {"answer": "Just how proud I am of myself, really, Piers.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 473, "question": "What have you learned about yourself on this crazy show biz roll you've been on?", "qSentId": 472}, {"answer": "You know the best thing about it, when I was -- I lost my father when I was 5 years old.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 482, "question": "What were the values they wanted you to have?", "qSentId": 481}, {"answer": "You asked Siri every day, presumably.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 504, "question": "Can you believe that?", "qSentId": 503}, {"answer": "Gosh, you know, I'm -- I don't take anything for granted.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 515, "question": "What is the next big ambition for you?", "qSentId": 514}, {"answer": "No, I don't look at it as empire.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 521, "question": "Do you have the empire building ambition of someone like Ryan Seacrest, who you've often been compared with?", "qSentId": 520}, {"answer": "That's not the kind of show I would like to produce, personally.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 531, "question": "You don't buy into the purity of the Kardashian lifestyle?", "qSentId": 530}, {"answer": "I think -- I'm excited.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 535, "question": "What do you think of Britney Spears joining the \"X Factor\"?", "qSentId": 534}, {"answer": "Yes.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 577, "question": "Is this true?", "qSentId": 576}, {"answer": "First of all, that term Hollywood royalty really, really scares me.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 610, "question": "But it is a wonderful story, isn't it?", "qSentId": 609}, {"answer": "My gosh, that's a very -- that's a very heady question there.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 645, "question": "And what should America and Americans be doing, do you think, to restore it?", "qSentId": 644}, {"answer": "Definitely.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 661, "question": "Don't you think?", "qSentId": 660}, {"answer": "Under the right circumstances, probably.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 694, "question": "If I suddenly went, shut down, cry in five minutes, could you do that like that?", "qSentId": 693}, {"answer": "Well --", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 697, "question": "What do you tell yourself to make yourself cry?", "qSentId": 696}, {"answer": "Yeah, you can't go there.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 699, "question": "Terrible things?", "qSentId": 698}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 704, "question": "You literally think of awful things?", "qSentId": 703}, {"answer": "Yes, it is.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 839, "question": "It's so unnatural, isn't it?", "qSentId": 838}, {"answer": "Well, I feel that like we're supposed to have forgiving hearts.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 852, "question": "What do you feel, Tito, about Conrad Murray?", "qSentId": 851}, {"answer": "Sure I forgive him.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 857, "question": "Do you forgive him?", "qSentId": 856}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 859, "question": "Do you all feel that way?", "qSentId": 858}, {"answer": "No.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 861, "question": "You don't, Jermaine?", "qSentId": 860}, {"answer": "I feel like it's just negligence and not -- it's on his part plus others.", "docId": "120511pmt", "aSentId": 864, "question": "What do you feel?", "qSentId": 863}]